I always believed we would see each other again
ฉันเชื่อมาตลอดว่าเราจะต้องได้พบกันอีก
That our days of separation would finally end
เชื่อว่าวันแห่งการจากลาจะสิ้นสุดลงในที่สุด
And all my troubles would be behind me...
ฉันจะทิ้งปัญหาทั้งหมดไว้เบื้องหลัง...
If only things could stay this way forever...
ถ้าชีวิตเช่นนี้สามารถคงอยู่ตลอดไป...
...A nightmare?
ฝันร้ายเหรอ?
Curious... If you're relaxed, shouldn't your dreams be pleasant?
ไม่น่าใช่นะ เวลาที่ผู้คนผ่อนคลายก็ควรจะฝันดีสิ
It was a good dream. It's just...
เป็นฝันดี เพียงแต่ว่า...
You weren't ready to wake up
แค่ไม่อยากตื่นขึ้นมางั้นเหรอ?
Eloquent as one may be, words of comfort are not one's strong suit
ข้าเชี่ยวชาญการพูดคุย แต่ปลอบโยนผู้อื่นไม่เก่งนัก
You are doing all you can
เจ้าพยายามมามากแล้วล่ะ
One can see your strength of will, your fearlessness in the face of danger
ข้ารู้ว่าเจ้ามีเจตจำนงที่แน่วแน่มาก และไม่เคยหวาดกลัวต่ออันตรายใด ๆ
And so, whatever your dream may be
เพราะฉะนั้น ไม่ว่ามันจะเป็น "ความฝัน" แบบไหน
One believes that... you shall achieve it
ข้าก็เชื่อว่าเจ้าจะทำให้มันเป็นจริงได้แน่
Of course, whenever the perils you face overwhelm you
และแน่นอนว่าหากเจ้าพานพบภัยอันตรายระหว่างทาง
Or you become weary, one is always here for you
หรือรู้สึกเหนื่อยล้าเต็มที ก็มาหาข้าได้เสมอ
After all... As an elder, it is only right to look out for the young ones
อย่างไรเสีย... ถ้าว่ากันตามอายุแล้ว ข้าก็นับว่าเป็น "ผู้อาวุโส" ของเจ้านั่นแหละ